etabu.com 2018-10-10

# etabu

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ETABU collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a 'User') of the http://etabu.com/ website. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by ETABU. 

**Personal identiﬁcation information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways. including, but not limited to. when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter. and in connection with other activities. services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for. as appropriate. name, email address. mailing address. Users may. however. visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities- 

**Non-personal identiﬁcation information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

**How we use collected information**

ETABU may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes: - To personalize user experience We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. — To send periodic emails We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries. questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt—in to our mailing list. they will receive emails that may include company news, updates. related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails. we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site. 

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection. storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access. alteration. disclosure or destruction of your personal information, usemame. password. transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

**Sharing you personal information**

We do not sell. trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners. trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. 

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.etabu.com makes use of log ﬁles. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP) addresses. type of browser. Internet Service Provider ( ISP ). date/time stamp. referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and web Beacons**

www.etabu.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-speciﬁc information on which pages the user access or visit. customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**Doubleclick DART cookie**  
\- Google, as a third party vendor. uses cookies to serve ads on www.etabu.com. 

\- Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.etabu.com and other sites on the Internet. 

— Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.php 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.etabu.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. 

Other technologies ( such as cookies. Javascript. or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. www.etabu.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. wvvw.etabu.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with speciﬁc web browsers can be found at the browsers‘ respective websites. 

**changes to this privacy policy**

ETABU has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. when we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modiﬁcations. 

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site. you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service- If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy. the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.
